mutwatch.com 2015-11-10

# PrivacyPolicy - MUTWatch

## MUTWATCH.COM PRIVACY POLICY

Last updated October 12, 205  
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which this website ("Site", "We", "Us") collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users ("Users") of the Site. This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by it. 

### Personal identification information

Email addresses are collected only from users who wish to Sign In to the site. The email address will only be used for the purpose of sending password reset emails or in case the user has submitted an error report. Email addresses will not be sold or distributed. 

### Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with the Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to the Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. 

### Web browser cookies

The Site uses "cookies" to enhance User experience. Users' web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track non-personal information about them. Users may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly. 

### How we use collected information

The Site collects and uses Users' non-personal information for the following purposes: \- To personalize Users' experience We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on the Site. \- To improve the Site We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from Users. 

### How we protect Users' information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of Users' information and data stored on the Site. 

### Sharing your non-personal information

We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf. 

### Google Adsense

We may use third-party advertising companies, such Google, to serve ads when Users visit the Site. These companies may use information about Users' interests in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to Users. If Users would like more information about this practice and to know their choices about not having this information used by these companies, see the Digital Advertising Alliance's or Network Advertising Initiative's website. 

### Children's Privacy

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. We take children's privacy seriously, and encourage parents to play an active role in their children's online experience at all times. 

### Changes to this privacy policy

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time and we will post all changes on this page. 

### Your acceptance of these terms

By using the Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use the Site. Your continued use of the Site will be deemed your acceptance of this policy. 

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices of the Site, please contact us at privacy at mail dot mutwatch dot com Thank you for your patience in reading our privacy policy.
